[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Does that mean I'm lying to you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "mean", "I", "'m", "lying", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Robert, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Robert", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, I'm not nearly as interesting as you just described.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "nearly", "as", "interesting", "as", "you", "just", "described", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Do I look like that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "look", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "You do.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "And I've been roaming around the country and doing -- what the hell have I been doing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "'ve", "been", "roaming", "around", "the", "country", "and", "doing", "--", "what", "the", "hell", "have", "I", "been", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", ":", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Communicate with them through Facebook and stuff, right?", "question_tokens": ["Communicate", "with", "them", "through", "Facebook", "and", "stuff", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I had a Facebook.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "Facebook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Did I really live this thing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "really", "live", "this", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "How much of it -- I mean you've ridden this extraordinary book.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "it", "--", "I", "mean", "you", "'ve", "ridden", "this", "extraordinary", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Well, because she was the woman that was doing these at the time, right?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "she", "was", "the", "woman", "that", "was", "doing", "these", "at", "the", "time", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I -- OK, I'll get serious for just a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "OK", ",", "I", "'ll", "get", "serious", "for", "just", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "How much do you blame your parents?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "blame", "your", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I don't blame anybody.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "blame", "anybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Did they ever tell you that they loved you, your parents?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "ever", "tell", "you", "that", "they", "loved", "you", ",", "your", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "LAKE: Never.", "answer_tokens": ["LAKE", ":", "Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "But although you don't necessarily blame them because of your belief in God, how much do you think did it damage your character, damage your personality, make you a damaged person?", "question_tokens": ["But", "although", "you", "do", "n't", "necessarily", "blame", "them", "because", "of", "your", "belief", "in", "God", ",", "how", "much", "do", "you", "think", "did", "it", "damage", "your", "character", ",", "damage", "your", "personality", ",", "make", "you", "a", "damaged", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Oh, I think that if I came from a different family, I would have been a very different person.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "that", "if", "I", "came", "from", "a", "different", "family", ",", "I", "would", "have", "been", "a", "very", "different", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Are you capable of love?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "capable", "of", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", ":", "NN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "How could you not love a God that kept you in the womb when you were supposed to be dead out of the womb?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "you", "not", "love", "a", "God", "that", "kept", "you", "in", "the", "womb", "when", "you", "were", "supposed", "to", "be", "dead", "out", "of", "the", "womb", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Let's -- let's take a short break, Robert.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "--", "let", "'s", "take", "a", "short", "break", ",", "Robert", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Could I just say one word about this?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "I", "just", "say", "one", "word", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Now what would you like to hear?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "what", "would", "you", "like", "to", "hear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "What your relationship was like with her before she died.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "your", "relationship", "was", "like", "with", "her", "before", "she", "died", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Did you love her, though?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "love", "her", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bonnie"]}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Did you know everything about her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "everything", "about", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Nobody ever knows -- everything and I -- particularly a person like Bonnie.", "answer_tokens": ["Nobody", "ever", "knows", "--", "everything", "and", "I", "--", "particularly", "a", "person", "like", "Bonnie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Was she a con artist?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "a", "con", "artist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I think she was a con artist, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "was", "a", "con", "artist", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Rewind?", "question_tokens": ["Rewind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Do you believe that --", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Does that mean I'm lying to you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "mean", "I", "'m", "lying", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "What did you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "I'm saying I've met you for, what, 20 minutes?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "saying", "I", "'ve", "met", "you", "for", ",", "what", ",", "20", "minutes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I don't care about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "care", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Why are you being so defensive?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "being", "so", "defensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Because you just insulted me.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "you", "just", "insulted", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What the hell is the difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "is", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I said I'm going to ask you --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "ask", "you", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Did you hear what I said?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "hear", "what", "I", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "-- well documented -- I heard what you said.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "well", "documented", "--", "I", "heard", "what", "you", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "You mean physically faithful?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "physically", "faithful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Do you represent some of those people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "represent", "some", "of", "those", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I don't represent anybody.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "represent", "anybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Do you know why I was arrested?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "why", "I", "was", "arrested", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "ORGAN: Tell me.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Tell", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You got any idea why, why I was under arrest for four years and he was under arrest for an hour, Mr. Research?", "question_tokens": ["You", "got", "any", "idea", "why", ",", "why", "I", "was", "under", "arrest", "for", "four", "years", "and", "he", "was", "under", "arrest", "for", "an", "hour", ",", "Mr.", "Research", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Research"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Why were you found liable?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "found", "liable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I told you why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "told", "you", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I would have been -- I -- if you were -- if you were the lawyer on that side, I took the stand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "been", "--", "I", "--", "if", "you", "were", "--", "if", "you", "were", "the", "lawyer", "on", "that", "side", ",", "I", "took", "the", "stand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Do you remember the night that she died well, or is it now something you've blocked out of your head?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "the", "night", "that", "she", "died", "well", ",", "or", "is", "it", "now", "something", "you", "'ve", "blocked", "out", "of", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "No, I remember it quite well.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "remember", "it", "quite", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "I'm interested in what happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "interested", "in", "what", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What the hell are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Let me help you.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "help", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Now you want to know what happened that night?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "you", "want", "to", "know", "what", "happened", "that", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "-- on your story.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "on", "your", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 519, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I'm curious about --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "curious", "about", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Am I right so far?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "So far.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "far", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "So I'm factually correct?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "'m", "factually", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "No, but your questions are boring, because I mean even what you just said, are you sure the people at Tibet give a (EXPLETIVE DELETED) about any of this?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "your", "questions", "are", "boring", ",", "because", "I", "mean", "even", "what", "you", "just", "said", ",", "are", "you", "sure", "the", "people", "at", "Tibet", "give", "a", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "about", "any", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I think you're here because you've written a book about your life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "here", "because", "you", "'ve", "written", "a", "book", "about", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tibet"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Than the murder of your wife?", "question_tokens": ["Than", "the", "murder", "of", "your", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I didn't murder my wife.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "murder", "my", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Because it's stupid.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "stupid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "What the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) is the matter with you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "is", "the", "matter", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "I didn't say you killed her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "say", "you", "killed", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Why don't you ask me some really interesting questions?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "ask", "me", "some", "really", "interesting", "questions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I said that you were acquitted in the court case but you were then --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "that", "you", "were", "acquitted", "in", "the", "court", "case", "but", "you", "were", "then", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "You are curious about why I was found liable?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "curious", "about", "why", "I", "was", "found", "liable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I'm curious about how you deal with the fact that a civil action was successfully brought against you for killing your wife.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "curious", "about", "how", "you", "deal", "with", "the", "fact", "that", "a", "civil", "action", "was", "successfully", "brought", "against", "you", "for", "killing", "your", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "What have I said to you that's factually inaccurate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "I", "said", "to", "you", "that", "'s", "factually", "inaccurate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "It's not so much factually inaccurate.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "so", "much", "factually", "inaccurate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Hasn't it ruined your life?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "n't", "it", "ruined", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "What -- that's another matter, Charlie.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "--", "that", "'s", "another", "matter", ",", "Charlie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Does it -- is that boring, the fact that this incident ruined your life?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "--", "is", "that", "boring", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "this", "incident", "ruined", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "We're not talking about how my life was ruined.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "not", "talking", "about", "how", "my", "life", "was", "ruined", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Don't you feel at all silly?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "feel", "at", "all", "silly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "I've said nothing about you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "said", "nothing", "about", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "With all that you've been able to find out since that night, who do you think killed Bonnie?", "question_tokens": ["With", "all", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "able", "to", "find", "out", "since", "that", "night", ",", "who", "do", "you", "think", "killed", "Bonnie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "It's not what I've been able to find out since that night.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "what", "I", "'ve", "been", "able", "to", "find", "out", "since", "that", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bonnie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "You can't go through your life feeling like this, surely.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "go", "through", "your", "life", "feeling", "like", "this", ",", "surely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Which of your Hollywood friends stood by you?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "of", "your", "Hollywood", "friends", "stood", "by", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "I don't have any Hollywood friends.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "Hollywood", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "No one at all?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["98 percent"]}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "I'm grateful to God that I lived long enough to find out that 98 percent of my personal life was (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "grateful", "to", "God", "that", "I", "lived", "long", "enough", "to", "find", "out", "that", "98", "percent", "of", "my", "personal", "life", "was", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Where do you live now?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "live", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "I live in an apartment, I told you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "live", "in", "an", "apartment", ",", "I", "told", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Do you have any women in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "women", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Well, like I told you, I've been on the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) for quite a long time now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "I", "told", "you", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "on", "the", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "for", "quite", "a", "long", "time", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120711pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "Which was the relationship with an audience and acting.", "answer_tokens": ["Which", "was", "the", "relationship", "with", "an", "audience", "and", "acting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]